Academic Affairs and Provost, Office of Senior V.P. for; Records ua500
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Bulletins, 1845 - 2017 May 17; 2; 11.75 cubic ft.; 65 captures
  - Graduate Bulletin Web Page, 2008 July 16 - 2017 May 17; 65 captures
    - Graduate Bulletin - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 October 17
      downloaded_count: 239164
      download_failures: 276
      warc_revisit_count: 202548
      warc_url_count: 239075
      total_data_in_kbs: 61075441
      duplicate_bytes: 53769145120
      warc_compressed_bytes: 6127282356
      doc_rate: 0.54
      kb_rate: 138.0
    - WARC file for Graduate Bulletin - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 October 17
    - Graduate Bulletin - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 January 17
    - WARC file for Graduate Bulletin - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 January 17
    - Graduate Bulletin - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 March 17
    - WARC file for Graduate Bulletin - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 March 17
    - Graduate Bulletin - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 August 17
    - WARC file for Graduate Bulletin - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 August 17
    - Graduate Bulletin - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 January 17
    - WARC file for Graduate Bulletin - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 January 17
    - Graduate Bulletin - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 March 17
      crawl: 273971
      start_date: 2017-03-17T16:55:07Z
      original_start_date: 2017-03-17T16:55:07Z
      processing_end_date: 2017-03-22T22:25:00Z
      end_date: 2017-03-22T18:08:47Z
      elapsed_ms: 436406787
      discovered_count: 7409222
      novel_count: 690900
      duplicate_count: 1257496
      queued_count: 5460826
      downloaded_count: 1948396
      download_failures: 359
      warc_revisit_count: 1257455
      warc_url_count: 1948270
      total_data_in_kbs: 266864045
      duplicate_bytes: 245675593330
      warc_compressed_bytes: 1581675727
      doc_rate: 4.46
      kb_rate: 611.0
    - WARC file for Graduate Bulletin - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 March 17
    - Graduate Bulletin - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 May 17
    - WARC file for Graduate Bulletin - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 May 17
- Program Registration Letters, 1964-2023; 3; 0.67 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically by program or degree title.
  This consists letters from the State Education Department confirming registration, deactivation, and alteration of academic programs. Most letters cover a single degree or program, although some letters address multiple programs.
  - Accounting, M.S., 1974 May 22 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 1)
  - Accounting, M.S., 1986-1987 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 2)
  - Actuarial and Mathematical Sciences, B.S., 1995 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 3)
  - African/Afro-American Studies, B.A., M.A. - Title change from Afro-American Studies, 1978 December 1 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 4)
  - Anthropology, M.A.; Afro-American Studies, B.A., 1969 September 3 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 5)
  - Applied Chemistry, M.S., 2004 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 6)
  - Atmospheric Science, B.S./M.S. Combined Program, 1982 June 11 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 7)
  - Atmospheric Science, Ph.D., 1967 July 31 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 8)
  - Biodiversity, Conservation, and, Policy, M.S., 1996 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 9)
  - Biology, B.A./M.A. Combined Program, 1982 April 21 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 10)
  - Biology, B.S./M.S. Combined Program, 1986 September 29 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 11)
  - Biology - Forensic Molecular Biology, M.S., 2001 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 12)
  - Biometry and Statistics, M.S., 1989 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 13)
  - Biometry and Statistics, Ph.D., 1995 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 14)
  - Business Administration, B.A./M.B.A. Combined Programs, 1991 May 7 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 15)
    Includes the following undergraduate degrees combined with an M.B.A.: Art, B.A.; Chinese Studies, B.A.; Greek and Roman Civilization, B.A.; Greek, B.A.; Latin, B.A.; Interdisciplinary Studies, B.A.; English, B.A.; French, B.A.; German, B.A.; Spanish, B.A.; Italian, B.A.; Linguistics, B.A.; Music, B.A.; Philosophy, B.A.; Russian, B.A.; Theatre, B.A.; Women's Studies, B.A.; Biology, B.A.; Mathematics, B.A.; African/Afro-American Studies, B.A.; Anthropology, B.A.; Asian Studies, B.A.; Rhetoric and Communications, B.A.; Economics, B.A.; Geography, B.A.; History, B.A.; Latin American Studies, B.A.; Puerto Rican Studies, B.A.; Psychology, B.A.; Russian and East European Studies, B.A.; Sociology, B.A.; Criminal Justice, B.A.; Political Science, B.A.; Interdisciplinary Studies, B.S.
  - Chemistry, B.S./M.S. Combined Program, 1982 April 21 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 16)
  - Chemistry, Ph.D., 1981 September 4 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 17)
  - Classics, M.A. - Program change from Latin, M.A., 1981 May 4 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 18)
  - Clinical Psychology, Ph.D., 2001 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 19)
  - Communication, M.A.; Rhetoric and Communication/Communication, B.A./M.A., 1990 April 6 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 20)
  - Computer Science, B.S./M.S.; Geology, B.S./M.S.; Geography, B.A./M.A. Combined Programs, 1982 April 15 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 21)
  - Computer Science and Applied Mathematics, B.S./Mathematics, M.A. Combined Program, 1982 April 21 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 22)
  - Computer Science, B.S., 1985 August 5 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 23)
  - Computer Science, B.A., 1986 April 4 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 24)
  - Computer Science, Ph.D., 1981-1982 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 25)
  - Computer Science, Ph.D., 1997 April 30 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 26)
  - Counseling, M.S. - Program change from School Counselor, M.S., 1983 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 27)
  - Counseling Psychology, Ph.D., 1981 July 10 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 28)
  - Counseling Psychology, Ph.D., 2001 December 17 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 29)
  - Counseling Psychology and Student Development, Ed.D. - Title change from Counseling and Personnel Services, Ed.D., 1978 November 21 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 30)
  - Court Systems Management, Certificate of Advanced Study, 1982 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 31)
  - Criminal Justice, B.A., M.A., 1985 March 1 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 32)
  - Criminal Justice, M.A./Social Welfare Management, M.S.W., Combined Program, 1985 August 6 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 33)
  - Criminal Justice, M.A./Social Work, M.S.W. - Combined Program, 1984 September 6 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 34)
  - Curriculum and Instruction, Reading - Ed.D. to Ph.D. conversions, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 35)
  - Curriculum Development and Instructional Technology, M.S. - Title change from Curriculum Planning and Development, M.S., 1987 May 11 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 36)
  - Curriculum Planning and Development, M.S. - Title change from Curriculum and Instruction, M.S., 1981 May 1 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 37)
  - Demography, Advanced Certificate, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 38)
  - Distance Learning, 2002 January 14 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 39)
  - Economics, B.A. or B.S./Public Administration, M.P.A. Combined Program, 1983 February 1 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 40)
  - Educational Administration, M.S., 1985 August 13 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 41)
  - Educational Administration and Policy Studies - Ed.D. to Ph.D. conversion, 1999-2000 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 42)
  - Educational Communications, M.S., Certificate of Advanced Study, 1981 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 43)
  - Educational Psychology and Statistics, M.S.; Educational Research, Certificate of Advanced Study, 1981 May 4 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 44)
  - English B.A./M.A. Combined Program, 1984 September 24 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 45)
  - English D.A. - Deactivation, 1995 May 12 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 46)
  - English, Ph.D.; French Studies, Ph.D.; History, Ph.D., 1992 December 2 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 47)
  - English/Library Science, M.A./M.L.S. Combined Program, 1989 February 21 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 48)
  - Environmental Health and Toxicology, M.S., Ph.D.; Biomedical Sciences, M.S., Ph.D., 1985 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 49)
  - Epidemiology, M.S., 1988 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 50)
  - Epidemiology, Ph.D., 1994 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 51)
  - Forensic Biology, M.S., 2003 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 52)
  - French, B.A./M.A. Combined Program, 1981 August 13 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 53)
  - French Studies, Ph.D., 1991 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 54)
  - French Studies, Ph.D.; Spanish, Ph.D.; English, Ph.D.; Philosophy, Ph.D., 1996 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 55)
  - General Professional Studies, M.S., 1981 May 11 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 56)
  - Geographic Information Systems and Spatial Analysis, Advanced Certificate, 1987-1988 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 57)
  - Geographic Information Systems and Spatial Analysis, Certificate, 1987-1988 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 58)
  - Geography, M.A., 1970 July 11 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 59)
  - German, Ph.D.; English, D.A., 1998 September 24 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 60)
  - Health Policy and Management, M.S., 1990 November 13 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 61)
  - History, B.A./M.A. Combined Program, 1981 August 13 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 62)
  - History, M.A./Public Affairs and Policy, M.A. - Multi-Award Degree Program, 2002 December 2 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 63)
  - History of Science, M.S., Ph.D.; Philosophy, Ph.D., 1970 July 14 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 64)
  - History/Library Science, M.A./M.L.S. Combined Program, 1989 February 27 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 65)
  - History/Public Affairs, M.A. Combined Program, 1987 February 18 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 66)
  - Humanistic Studies, D.A. - Deactivation, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 67)
  - Information Science, M.S., 1991 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 68)
  - Information Science, Ph.D., 1990 August 8 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 69)
  - Interdisciplinary Studies (Mediterranean Archaeology), B.A./Classics, M.A. - Combined Program, 1983 March 21 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 70)
  - Joint SUNY Albany and Albany Law School of Union University Program - Public Administration, M.P.A./Law, J.D., 1982 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 71)
  - Joint SUNY Albany and Albany Law School of Union University Programs - Law, B.A./J.D., B.S./J.D., 1989 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 72)
  - Joint SUNY Albany and Albany Law School Program - Social Work, M.S.W./Law, J.D., 2000 March 15 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 73)
  - Joint SUNY Albany and New York State Department of Health Program - Public Health, M.P.H., 1990 May 22 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 74)
  - Joint SUNY Albany and New York State Department of Health Programs - Health Policy and Management, M.S.; Environmental and Occupational Health, M.S., 1991 November 25 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 75)
  - Joint SUNY Albany and SUNY College of Optometry Program - Biology, B.S./Optometry, O.D., 1995 March 22 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 76)
  - Joint SUNY Albany and SUNY New Paltz Program - Sociology, M.A./Sociology, M.S.W., 1996 July 25 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 77)
  - Latin, B.A./M.A. Combined Program, 1981 August 13 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 78)
  - Latin American and Caribbean Studies, Advanced Certificate, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 79)
  - Latin American and Caribbean Studies, M.A., 1988 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 80)
  - Liberal Studies, M.A., 1977 September 8 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 81)
  - Library and Information Science, Advanced Certificate, 1978 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 82)
  - Library Science, B.A./M.L.S., B.S./M.L.S. Combined Programs, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 83)
    Includes the following degrees combined with an M.L.S.: Linguistics, B.A.; Rhetoric and Communications, B.A.; Philosophy, B.A.; Mathematics, B.A.; Mathematics "7-12", B.A.; Psychology, B.A.; Public Affairs, B.A.; Criminal Justice, B.A.; Social Studies "7-12", B.A.; Anthropology, B.A.; Economics, B.A.; Greek and Roman Civilization, B.A.; History, B.A.; Geography, B.A.; Political Science, B.A.; Sociology, B.A.; African and Afro-American Studies, B.A.; Interdisciplinary Studies, B.A.; Biology, B.S.; Biology "7-12", B.S.; Business Administration, B.S.; Computer Science and Applied Mathematics, B.S.; Computer Science, B.S.; Business Education, B.S.; Business and Distributive Education, B.S.; Medical Technology, B.S.; Mathematics, B.S.; Mathematics "7-12", B.S.; Physics, B.S.; Physics "7-12", B.S.; Chemistry, B.S.; Chemistry "7-12", B.S.; Atmospheric Science, B.S.; Geology, B.S.; Earth Science "7-12", B.S.; Social Welfare, B.S.; Economics, B.S.; Interdisciplinary Studies, B.S.; Asian Studies, B.A.; Russian and East European Studies, B.A.; Latin American Studies, B.A.; Puerto Rican Studies, B.A.; Judaic Studies, B.A.; Biology, B.A.; Art, B.A.; Music, B.A.; Theatre, B.A.; French, B.A.; French "7-12", B.A.; German, B.A.; German "7-12", B.A.; Italian, B.A.; Italian "7-12", B.A.; Spanish, B.A.; Spanish "7-12", B.A.; Russian, B.A.; Russian "7-12", B.A., Chinese Studies, B.A.; Latin, B.A.; Latin "7-12", B.A.; Greek, B.A.; English, B.A.; English "7-12", B.A.
  - Library Science, M.L.S., 1966 June 22 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 84)
  - Linguistics, B.A./Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages, M.S. Combined Program, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 85)
  - Mathematics, B.A./M.A. Combined Program, 1982 June 11 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 86)
  - Mathematics, B.S./M.A. Combined Program, 1982 April 21 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 87)
  - Mathematics, Ph.D., 1981-1982 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 88)
  - Nanosciences and Nanoengineering, M.S., Ph.D., 2003 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 89)
  - Nursing, B.S., 1967 July (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 90)
  - Organizational Studies, Ph.D., 1985 December 16 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 91)
  - Philosophy, B.A./M.A. Combined Program, 1981 August 13 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 92)
  - Philosophy, Ph.D., 1993 April 6 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 93)
  - Physics B.S./M.S. Combined Program, 1982 June 11 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 94)
  - Planning and Policy Analysis, Advanced Certificate, 1979 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 95)
  - Political Science, B.A./M.A. Combined Program, 1982 June 11 (Box 1 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 96)
  - Political Science, B.A./Public Administration, M.P.A. Combined Program, 1983 February 1 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 1)
  - Psychology, M.A., Ph.D., 1985 December 2 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 2)
  - Psychology, Ph.D.s, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 3)
    Covers the following degrees: Psychology, Ph.D. (Deleted); Educational Psychology, Ph.D.; Counseling Psychology, Ph.D.; School Psychology, Psy.D.; Biopsychology, Ph.D.; Clinical Psychology, Ph.d.; Cognitive Psychology, Ph.D.; Social/Personality Psychology, Ph.D.
  - Educational Psychology, Ph.D.; School Psychology, Psy.D.; Biopsychology, Ph.D.; Cognitive Psychology, Ph.D., 1994 November 10 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 4)
  - Psychology/Counseling, B.A./M.S. Combined Program, 1984 August 6 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 5)
  - Psychology/Rehabilitation Counseling, B.A./M.S. Combined Program, 1984 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 6)
  - Public Administration, Ph.D. - Degree change from Public Administration, D.P.A., 1987-1988 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 7)
  - Public Affairs and Policy, M.A. - Title change from Public Affairs, M.A., 1983 January 24 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 8)
  - Public Health, D.P.H., 1995 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 9)
  - Public History, Advanced Certificate, 1983 May 5 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 10)
  - Public Management, Certificate of Graduate Study, 1983 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 11)
  - Public Sector Management, Advanced Certificate, 1987 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 12)
  - Reading, Certificate of Advanced Study, 1981 May 4 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 13)
  - Reading, M.S., 1977 July 25 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 14)
  - Regional Planning, M.R.P., 1980 October 2 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 15)
  - Regional Planning, M.R.P., 1982 February 23 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 16)
  - Regulatory Economics, Certificate, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 17)
  - Rehabilitation Counseling, M.S., 1981 May 11 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 18)
  - Rhetoric and Communications, B.A./M.A. Combined Program, 1982 June 11 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 19)
  - Rhetoric and Communications, M.A., 1981 May 4 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 20)
  - Russian, B.A./M.A. Combined Program, 1981 August 13 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 21)
  - Russian, 7-12, B.A./M.A. Combined Program, 1982 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 22)
  - School Counselor, M.S.; Counseling and Personnel Services, Advanced Certificate, 1981 May 14 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 23)
  - School District Administrator, Ed.D.; School Administrator and Supervisor, Advanced Certificate, Ed.D., 1978 November 17 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 24)
  - School of Education, Various Graduate Programs, 1971 May 21 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 25)
  - *School of Education, Program Deactivations - Educational Foundations, Ph.D.; School District Administrator, Ed.D.; School Adminstrator and Supervisor, Ed.D.; Counseling and Personnel Services, Ed.D., 1983 August (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 26)
  - School Psychology, Psy.D., 1985 October 23 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 27)
  - School Psychology, Psy.D., 1993 August 24 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 28)
  - School Psychology, Psy.D., 2001 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 29)
  - Social Welfare, B.S., Ph.D., 1971 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 30)
  - Social Welfare, M.S.W., 1970 November 19 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 31)
  - Social Welfare, M.S.W./Ph.D. Combined Program, 1987 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 32)
  - Social Welfare, Ph.D., 1982; 1984 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 33)
  - Sociology, B.A./M.A. Combined Program, 1981 August 13 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 34)
  - Sociology, B.A./Public Administration, M.P.A. Combined Program, 1983 February 1 (Box 2 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 35)
  - Spanish, B.A./M.A. Combined Program, 1982 April 21 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 1)
  - Spanish, Ph.D. - Latin American, Caribbean, and U.S. Latino Cultural Studies Concentration, 1998-1999 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 2)
  - Special Education, M.S., 1978 July 13 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 3)
  - Special Education, M.S., 1996 January 19 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 4)
  - Studio Art, M.F.A., 1981-1982 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 5)
  - Taxation, M.S., 1987 January 26 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 6)
  - Taxation, M.S., 1994 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 7)
  - Taxation, M.S., 2000 December 26 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 8)
  - Teacher of Special Education, M.S., 1976 June 8 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 9)
  - Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages, M.S., 1981 May 11 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 10)
  - Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages, M.S., 1983 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 11)
  - Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages, M.S., 1994 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 12)
  - Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages, M.S., 2001 September (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 13)
  - Theatre, B.A./M.A. Combined Program; Public Affairs, B.A./M.A. Combined Program, 1985 December 30 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 14)
  - Urban and Regional Planning, M.R.P., 1986 May 2 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 15)
  - Urban Education, Advanced Certificate, 1997 April 29 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 16)
  - Urban Policy, Certificate, 1987 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 17)
  - Various B.A./M.A. Combined Programs, 1981 September 30 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 18)
    Includes: Russian, B.A./M.A.; Philosophy, B.A./M.A.; Sociology, B.A./M.A.; History, B.A./M.A.; Latin, B.A./M.A.; French, B.A./M.A.
  - Various B.A./M.A. and B.S./M.S. Combined Programs, 1982 July 23 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 19)
    Includes: Rhetoric and Communications, B.A./M.A.; Mathematics, B.A./M.A.; Physics, B.S./M.S.; Atmospheric Science, B.S./M.S.; Political Science, B.A./M.A.
  - Various B.A./M.P.A. and B.S./M.P.A. Combined Programs, 1983 March 24 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 20)
    Includes: Economics/Public Administration, B.A./M.P.A.; Economics/Public Administration, B.S./M.P.A.; Political Science/Public Administration, B.A./M.P.A.; Sociology/Public Administration, B.A./M.P.A.
  - Various Graduate Programs, 1964 March 31 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 21)
    Includes the following programs: American History, Ph.D.; English, Ph.D.; Psychology, Ph.D.; Curriculums and Supervision, Ed.D.; Educational Administration, Ed.D.; Guidance and Personnel Services, Ed.D.; Reading, Ed.D.; Librarianship, M.L.S.; and the following M.A. or M.S. degrees: Biology; Chemistry; Physics; Business; Education (Secondary-School Teaching, Developmental Reading, Guidance Service, General Professional Studies); English Literature; French; German; Latin; Spanish; Mathematics; Psychology; Social Studies; History; Speech.
  - Various Graduate Programs - Discontinuance, 1996 September 27 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 22)